designsmag.com 2016-06-28

# Privacy Policy of Designsmag (Designs Magazine)

## Privacy Policy

When you reached Designsmag.com, the privacy of our respected visitors is of great importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Designsmag and how it is used.

Email addresses are only provided by the user voluntarily through the commenting process or via e-mail communications. Authors’ personal information collected through 3rd party forms are also provided voluntarily and will remain confidential and abide by the terms stated in this privacy policy.

### Cookies And Web Beacons

Designsmag.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

  1. Whenever you click an ad, you do so freely and out of pure interest in the offer of a particular advertiser.
  2. The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads.
  3. When you visit a partner’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher’s site(s) and across the web.
  4. For more information about cookies, please see this video:

### What Are Cookies and How Do They Work

5\. If you want to learn more about the perks of using third party ad servers such as Google AdSense, please see these three videos:

### [Part1](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=prh9kf1Jbmw) |  [Part2 ](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Np2da3FND8Y) |[  Part3](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Np2da3FND8Y)

6\. Please, be aware that this whole system of cookies and collection of demographic information has a sole purpose of improving your online experience and any personal data through which you could be identified are impossible to obtain during the process.

7\. If you however want to prevent any advertising system from collecting information about your interests, please see this video for opt-out instructions:

### Opt-Out instructions

### Advertisements

Designsmag.com including any predecessor or affiliated companies, does not signify or ratify the accuracy or reliability of any of the advertisements (collectively), i.e. links, banners, downloads, distributions or other information accessed directly or indirectly from host advertisements contained on this website (Service), nor the quality of any products, information or other materials displayed, purchased or obtained by any consumer, as a result of an advertisement or any other information or offer in connection with the service or products.

We at Designsmag shall not be responsible for any errors or oversights contained within any 3rd party advertisements contained within its website, and reserve the right to make changes and adjust content without notice. Therefore, designsmag and 3rd party information are provided “AS IS.” You, the consumer, acknowledge that any reliance upon any materials shall be at your sole risk.

3rd party advertisers featured on designsmag may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this [Privacy Policy](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Privacy_policy "Privacy Policy"). The only information that they will be able to track is basic website usage information and other analytic.
